# TAYLOR PARKER

105 Dorroh Lane, East Ridge, TN 37412 | (C) 615-788-1823 | taylorparker2013@gmail.com

https://taylorparker.me

https://github.com/taylorparker

### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Student Front-End Web Developer currently pursuing a degree in Computer Science. Supportive team player with a passion for Web Design, as well as experience in hands-on projects involving Java, HTML, CSS, SASS, PHP, Bootstrap and JavaScript.

### **SKILLS**

3 Years of HTML Experience

3 Years of CSS Experience

3 Years of Bootstrap Experience

1 year of JavaScript Experience Less than 1 year of SASS Experience Less than 1 Year of PHP Experience

## WORK HISTORY

Apr 2018 - Jul 2018

Front End Web Developer | Tennessee Interventional and Imaging Associates
Redesigned existing website for viewing on all mobile devices
Worked with Monsido to meet WCAG 2.0
Migrated website hosting platform

Dec 2016 - Feb 2017

Front End Web Developer | Beussink & Hickam P.C
Created website based off a hand drawn design
Incorporated Facebook Messanger and Google Maps API
Used Bootstrap's grid for the front-end

# **EDUCATION**

Aug 2014 - Jul 2019

Bachelor of Science, Major in Computer Science, Minor in Business Administration University of Tennessee at Chattanooga, Chattanooga, TN